<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Applications on m1h4.github.io</title>
    <link>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Applications on m1h4.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://m1h4.github.io/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Resize</title>
      <link>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/photo-resize/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/photo-resize/</guid>
      <description>Photo Resize is a simple sharing extension for Android which helps you send photos via email or messaging more quickly. It creates a temporary smaller version of your photo before you send it so that you don’t have to send the full couple of megabytes of a 8MP photo via email.
You can find and follow Photo Resize on Google+.
Download The extension can be found on the Google Play by clicking the following link:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzed</title>
      <link>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/analyzed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/analyzed/</guid>
      <description>Analyzed is a simple plugin for Windows Media Player written to be compact and minimalistic. It is a upgrade to the old Barr plugin which is not supported anymore.
It was tested and is working on Windows Media Player 10, 11 and 12 (both 32-bit and 64-bit versions). It should work on older versions of the player but you might encounter problems like error messages appearing after you try to close Windows Media Player so I suggest that you upgrade to one of the tested versions if you haven’t already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Analyzer</title>
      <link>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/audio-analyzer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/audio-analyzer/</guid>
      <description>Audio Analyzer is an audio visualization application which you can use to make listening to music more interesting. It renders various visualizations in accordance to playing sounds.
Download Download Audio Analyzer version 2.7.0 and extract it using your favorite archiver.
Screenshots    Two screenshots showing Audio Analyzer in action.
Configuration Open the provided ReadMe.htm for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurve</title>
      <link>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/kurve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://m1h4.github.io/apps/kurve/</guid>
      <description>Kurve is a simple Windows multiplayer game you can play with your friends. The objective is to stay alive for as long as you can.
Download Download Kurve version 1.0.0 and extract it using your favorite archiver.
Controls Press Space to start a game after all players have joined by pressin their left key. Space continues after all players die/the game ends. Pause pauses/unpauses the game.
Red player: Left Arrow for left, Right Arrow for right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>